The model is to add a sticky layer to the collar and the collar plate.
Use the adjustment plate tool to select the collar and the collar plate.
In the property editor, pull down.
Find .
You can see that the plate of the 2D or 3D window is orange.
It means that the sticky layer has been added.
The collar and the collar need to apply the corresponding sticky layer type.
Select in the property editor.
Under the sticky layer, the physical properties preset column.
Click on the triangle on the right to list six sticky layers.
Select .
If it is the bottom collar of the suit, select .
Here, the sticky layer type, select .
Under each preset, you can click on the details to check the physical properties of the sticky layer.
In addition,
In order to prevent the seam line deformation of the seam allowance,
This position needs to be added to the sticky layer.
Use the adjustment plate tool.
Press the Shift key to select multiple lines.
In the property editor, select .
Set the width of the sticky layer.
After enlarging, find that the sticky layer is not extended to the outside of the plate at this point.
Come to the property editor.
Click on the triangle on the left to extend.
You can set the extension to the opening or the end.
Here, select the end.
Click on the triangle on the right.
Select .
The sticky layer can also select the physical properties preset.
The operation is the same as the sticky layer in the front.
In the 2D tool bar, above the sticker tool,
There is a sticky layer tool.
Select it.
The position of the sticky layer and the sticky layer will be highlighted.
Click on the position where the sticky layer needs to be added.
The sticky layer can be added.
Or the
Quickly add multiple sticky layers.
Click on the position.
You can delete the sticky layer.
Use the sticky layer tool to add the sticky layer position.
You can also edit its properties in the property editor.
On the plate, you can also add a partial sticky layer to the inner shape of the closed box.
Switch to the adjustment plate tool.
Click on the entire inner shape.
Click on the sticky layer in the property editor.
You can add a partial sticky layer.
If you don't want to show the orange sticky layer in the 3D window,
You can stop the mouse on the floating information display.
Close the display.
Sticky layer thinning.
Next, add the sticky layer to the sleeve and the bottom of the skirt.
There are two ways to make the sticky layer.
The sticky layer tool and the sticky layer plate.
Select the sticky layer tool in the 3D tool bar.
The position of the empty line can be added to the sticky layer.
Add the sticky layer to the bottom of the skirt.
The mouse is stopped at the bottom.
When the blue dot is displayed, it means that it can be added.
Click on the actual point.
In the bottom line, you can press the middle button to determine the direction.
Click on the double click.
The sticky layer added is completed.
In both the 3D window and 2D window, you can add the sticky layer.
Switch to the sticky layer tool or the moving tool.
The sticky layer is in the state of being selected.
In the property editor, you can set the basic information of the sticky layer.
The type is used to set the sticky layer on the inside, outside, or both sides.
Here is set as the inside.
The bottom can be used to check and modify the width of the sticker, the length column can be used to check the length of the sticker, and modify its length value or percentage, such as from 120% to 120% of the length.
You can see that the longer sticker will be transcended and the particle diameter and conflict thickness of the sticker can also be adjusted.
You can also choose the material of the sticker. The option only shows the material type available in the object window.
You can also set the slash line direction or set the slash line angle directly.
Click to select the next spot.
You can add a spot at the side of the sticker.
On the side of the sticker,
click the right button.
It can be used to mark the surface of the sticker.
It can also be used to mark the surface of the sticker.
Set the initialization, counter-activation, freeze and surface flip.
Next, use the side panel to make the side panel at the sleeve.
There is already a centimeter of inner line at the sleeve.
Use the hook outline tool and press the Shift key to select a circle of the line.
On the selected line, right-click and select Hook as panel.
The side panel of the hook will move with the mouse.
Press the blank button to place the side panel.
Use the adjustment panel tool to select it.
Press the Ctrl key and press the D key.
Press the side panel on the other side.
Use the sewing tool to sew the side panel to the sleeve.
In order to ensure that the side seam is even, the seam line at the bottom is folded.
Select the side panel in the 3D window.
On the panel, right-click and select Add to inside.
The side panel will be added to the inside of the sleeve panel with the sewing line.
And fit the shape of the sleeve.
Finally, simulate.
After the simulation is stable, turn off the simulation.
The side of the sleeve is finished.